Great work understanding JSON parsing this far.
到目前为止 你对 JSON 解析的理解非常到位
So, let's start looking more closely at some real USGS data and then gradually
那么 让我们更仔细地看一看 一些真实的 USGS 数据 然后逐步
build up the task to being able to record in your quick report app for
构建可记录于你的快速 报告应用以在 JSON 中
parse in JSON.
解析的任务
On the main PH for the USGS documentation, I want to scroll down to
在 USGS 文档的主要 PH 上 我想向下滚动至一个有关
a section about methods and then go to specific subsection called query.
方法的部分 然后转至 名为 query 的特定的分部
Now in this section, you have a few examples of URL queries that
现在 在这个部分中 你有 几个 URL 查询示例
you can make in order to get data back from the API.
你可创建这些它们以 从 API 重新获取数据
I'm going to take a variant on the second line to make it a little bit more
我打算在第二行获取一个变量 以使其处于最新状态
up to date and go ahead, and execute it.
并且我会继续执行它
So, this is the actual raw text response in GeoJSON format that you'll get back
那么 这是你在从 API 请求特定数据时将会返回的
when you are requesting specific data from API.
实际的原始文本响应 其采用 GeoJSON 格式
So now, its time to dig in to that data and
那么现在 是时候深入了解该数据并
retrieve the particular information that we want for our app.
检索我们所需的用于 应用的特定信息了
Now, one thing you probably noticed is that this in
现在 你可能已 注意到的一件事是
overwhelming a amount of text.
出现了大量的文本
There are no newline breaks, which is actually intended to make
没有任何换行符 其实际目的是要使
the response more compact and easier to transfer over the Internet.
响应变得更紧凑、更易于 通过 Internet 进行传输
But as a trade-off, it makes it really harder for us humans to read.
但是作为一个权衡 这将使我们人类 真的更难以读取
So fortunately, we can use a JSON formatting tool to format the JSON.
所以幸运的是 我们可以使用 JSON 格式化工具来格式化 JSON
So it's a little bit easier for us, humans to read and debug on our own.
这样一来 我们人类在自行 读取和排除故障时将变得更加轻松一点
The data will actually be the same, it'll just be presented to us with a few
数据实际上将会是相同的 只是在显示给我们时
more line breaks and spacing and we can search online for this type of tool.
换行符和空格会更多一些 并且我们可以在线搜索此类工具
So if you search for json formatter, you get a few options.
那么 如果你搜索 json 格式化程序 你将获得数个选项
Let's take a look at this first one, it looks pretty good.
让我们看一看第一个选项 它看上去非常不错
So I'm going to copy and paste the raw JSON that we got back from our original
因此我会将我们从原始测试 查询重新获得的原始 JSON
test query and I'm going to place it here in this JSON formatted tool,
进行复制粘贴 并且我会将其置于 该 JSON 格式化工具中的此处
then I'll go ahead and hit Process.
然后我们将继续查找程序
This is looking way better already.
这看起来已经更好了
So, let's go full screen to dive in.
那么 让我们使用全屏来深入了解一下
Cool.
非常棒
Now, this is really much more readable.
现在 可读性真的有所提高
And now, we have a lot of formatted JSON data that we can read through.
现在我们有许多已格式化的 JSON 数据可供我们通读
As you might notice,
正如你可能注意到的那样
there's a tree structure that we're probably familiar with.
有一个我们可能 非常熟悉的树结构
Something that you might see in your Windows Explore or Mac OS Finder and
你可能会在Windows Explore 或 Mac OS Finder 中看到的内容
it's much easier to read.
这样读起来容易多了
Notice that you have these minuses and plus buttons that allow you to expand
请注意 你有这些减号和 加号按钮 你可使用它们来展开
and collapse sub sections of the JSON response,
和折叠 JSON 响应的分部
which makes it much easier to read one section at a time.
这样一来你便可以更轻松地 同时读取一个部分
So when I route JSON object, when we're collapsed down here using the tool.
那么 当我路由 JSON 对象时 当我们被使用该工具在此处向下折叠时
We have a key here called features, which actually maps to a JSON array.
我们此时有一个名为 features 的键 其实际上映射到 JSON 数组
Again, we know that from the left and the right bracket.
此外 我们知道其位于 左右括号中
It turns out that this array actually contains what a feature means,
结果是 此数组实际上 包含一个特征作为
as a single earthquake.
单一地震的含义
So, each feature in this array or each element in this array actually maps to
因此 此数组中的每一个特征或者 此数组中的每一个元素实际上都映射到
the information for each specific earthquake.
每个特定 地震的信息
So if you look and we collapse a little bit here,
所以 如果你看一下 便会发现我们在此处折叠了一点
if you looked at the first element in the array and we expanded out,
如果你看一看此数组中的 第一个元素 便会发现我们已展开了
we see that it contains a JSON object with all the details,
我们看到其中包含一个 JSON 对象 该对象具有所有详细信息
all the meta information that we need for the first array.
我们所需要的第一个 数组的全部元信息
Similarly if we expand the second element,
同样 如果我们展开 第二个元素
we can see a similar set of data.
我们可看到一组相似的数据
So as you can see here, you can go one at a time through the array and
因此 正如你在此处所看到的那样 你可同时浏览数组中的一个部分
look at the specific information for
并且看一看每个地震特征
each earthquake feature return from our data request.
从我们的数据请求 返回的特定信息
That's pretty cool.
这相当不错
So, let's collapse down a little bit again.
那么 让我们再 向下折叠一点
Now back at the root of our JSON objects, we have four keys.
现在回到我们 JSON 对象的根 我们有四个键
We've got type, metadata, features and this thing called bbox.
我们有类型、元数据、 特征和这个名为 bbox 的项目
Now we're really just interested in the features key, because it contains
现在我们真的只是对 features 键感兴趣 因为其中包含
the array of all the earthquake data that we want for our app.
我们所需的用于我们的应用的 所有地震数据
Now you'll notice that the features array contains ten objects for now,
现在 你将注意到特征 数组到现在为止包含十个对象
because we actually asked for
因为当我们实际上查询 API 时
ten results when we actually queried the API.
我们实际上 请求了十个结果
Now, if you look at the first object in the array, we can see,
现在 如果你看一看数组中的 第一个对象 我们可以看到
if we collapse down that it also has four keys.
如果我们向下折叠 其也会有四个键
One called type, one called properties, one called geometry and
一个名为 type 一个名为 properties 一个名为 geometry
the last one being ID.
最后一个为 ID
All these four,
所有这四个键
it looks like the properties key has the information that we want.
都看起来像 properties 键 且具有我们所需的信息
Finally, we can see that the data or the JSON object that the properties key maps
最后 我们可以看到 properties 键 映射到的数据或 JSON 对象
to, if we expand out here, it contains a bunch of the keys and
如果我们在此处展开 其中将包含一系列键以及
the related data that we'll need for our app.
我们将需要的用于我们的应用的 相关数据
Here we've got the magnitude, the place, the time and
此时我们获得了震级、 地点、时间和
a user URL to point to more detail about the earthquake.
指向详细地震信息的 用户 URL
In this next quiz, you'll become more familiar with the key value pairs that
在这下一个练习中 你将对 来自 USGS API 的 JSON
are provided in the JSON response from the USGS API.
响应中所提供的键值对 更加熟悉
We're going to provide you with a query URL that
我们将为你提供 位于练习之下的注释中
linked in the note below the quiz.
所链接的查询 URL
First, I want you to copy the URL that we provided you and
首先 我想让你复制 我们为你提供的 URL
paste in to a web browser, then you'll get a JSON response back, but
并将其粘贴到 web 浏览器 然后你将重新获得一个 JSON 响应
it'll be a lot of text quizzed together.
这将是许多一起进行测试的文本
So, go ahead and put into a JSON formatter like we showed you earlier.
所以 继续进入 JSON 格式化程序 就像我们早期为你展示的那样
Then on a blank piece of paper, I want you to draw a sketch of what our query
然后 如果我们必须显示地震的 完整列表 我想让你在一张空白纸上
report app would look like if we had to display a whole list of earthquakes.
画一个草图来描绘我们 查询报告应用的外观
For the first quake on the list, I'm going to look at the JSON response to
对于该列表上的第一个地震 我将查看 JSON 响应
find the first earthquake in the futures array.
以在 futures 数组中 查找第一个地震
Now within that JSON object, I can find the magnitude key.
现在 在该 JSON 对象内 我可以找到 magnitude 键
The magnitude, in this case is 7.2.
在这种情况下 magnitude 为 7.2
So, I'm going to go ahead and just write that into our sketch.
因此 我打算继续 将其写入我们的草图
Follow the same process for the location and date for this earthquake.
对该地震的位置 和日期执行相同过程
You may have noticed that time is actually a really long number,
你可能已注意到 时间 实际上是一个非常长的数字
which is in milliseconds that have passed since January 1st, 1970.
其以毫秒为单位 始于 1970 年 1 月 1 日
This is known as Unix time.
这称为 Unix 时间
So if you wanted to know what the actual date that this corresponds to,
因此 如果你想知道 其所对应的实际日期是什么
you can actually find a tool online that converts time in milliseconds to
你实际上可以在线找到一个工具 来将以毫秒为单位的时间转换为
an actual date.
一个实际日期
I'll go ahead and leave an example in the notes.
我会继续 将一个示例保留在注释中
But for this quiz, for the sketch, you can leave the time in milliseconds.
但是 对于此练习 对于该草图 你可保留以毫秒为单位的时间
Now, you want to repeat those steps to finish writing in the information
现在 你想要重复那些步骤 以完成写入有关将填写于
about the rest of the earthquakes that will fill up the list.
列表之中的 地震的其余部分的信息